I'm just me why do you care for me when
we all follow this thing where do we go
come here spit it out what is it exactly
a plane is the amount cleaning you out
and my satisfactory today I'm thinking
about the things that are deadly the way
I'm drinking you don't like I want a job
like I wanna dance me step on the glass
staple your tongue bury your friend try
to wake up there your friend I want to
end
where do we go
listen keep you in the dark without you
expected me to make my heart like it was
star and get you connected me too
very a friend try to wake up
I wanna end why don't you run for me why
do you care for me when we all fall
asleep or do we go